<dashboard script="arcus_uber.js" stylesheet="arcus_uber.css">
	<label>Start</label>
	<description>This is the overview dashboard when the app loads.</description>
	<row id="arcus_header">
		<html>
			<h1>Uber Splunk App</h1>
			<h2>Rider Reporting</h2>
		</html>
	</row>
	<row>
		<panel>
			<html>
				<div class="arcus">
					<i class="title fas fa-car" />
					<span style="font-size:30px; font-weight: 100;">About Me</span>
					<hr />
					<p>For the past decade I've traveled around the country deploying big data solutions to hundreds of Splunk customers. Analytics is one of my passions: I love digging into the data and teasing out interesting observations you'd otherwise miss.</p>
					<p>
						<strong>The idea to build this app came from years of mentoring consultants.</strong>
						I found that teaching engineers the nuts and bolts of a platform is
						<i>relatively easy</i>
						. However, when faced with a complex challenge or sophisticated dataset I often see consultants get stuck:
					</p>
					<p>
						<ul>
							<li>Who is the audience you're seeking to serve?</li>
							<li>What meaningful questions are you trying to answer?</li>
							<li>What process or approach best serves the customer's needs?</li>
						</ul>
					</p>
					<p>
						<strong>I developed this app to teach engineers how to think.</strong>
						Building apps and visualizing data are my paintbrush and canvas. It's my art. I hope that by pulling back the curtain and showing you
						<i>the process</i>
						will make you a better big data practitioner.
					</p>
					<hr />
					<h2>
						<b>Tutorial Walkthrough:</b>
					</h2>
					<ol>
						<li>
							<a href="https://arcusdata.io">Planning Ahead - Tips &amp; approach for developing a Splunk app</a>
						</li>
						<li>
							<a href="https://arcusdata.io">Static Reports are Dead. Why all Splunk dashboards should be interactive</a>
						</li>
						<li>
							<a href="https://arcusdata.io">Listen to your customers! Incorporating feedback into your Splunk Use Cases</a>
						</li>
					</ol>
				</div>
			</html>
		</panel>
		<panel>
			<html>
				<div class="arcus">
					<i class="title fas fa-map-marker-alt" />
					<span style="font-size:30px; font-weight: 100;">Uber Use Cases</span>
					<hr />
					<p class="icon">
						<i class="fas fa-chart-line" />
						<a href="/app/arcus_uber_app/uber_dashboard">Executive Dashboard</a>
					</p>
					<p>Start off by visiting the Uber Executive Dashboard. This will give you high-level insights into key metrics. It'll also give you a chance to get familiar with the data.</p>
					<p class="icon">
						<i class="fas fa-chart-bar" />
						<a href="https://splunk.arcusdata.io/en-US/app/arcus_ppm_2.0/ppm_executive_view">Advanced Use Cases</a>
					</p>
					<p>When you're ready for a deep dive take look at the advanced use cases. These are tough questions I came up with and used Splunk searches to answer:</p>
					<ul>
						<li>What's the most expensive city?</li>
						<li>What time of year do I ride the most?</li>
						<li>Is there a correlation between time and price?</li>
						<li>Historical trending of total rides vs. cost?</li>
						<li>How long do I wait around for uber?</li>
					</ul>
					<hr />
					<p class="icon">
						<i class="fab fa-github" />
						<a href="https://github.com/arcus-data/arcus-uber-splunk-app">Fork on GitHub</a>
					</p>
					<p>What questions did you come up with? What additional use cases can you build with this data? I've open-sourced the code and made the data publicly available.  Try developing additional use cases and contribute back to the community.</p>
				</div>
			</html>
		</panel>
		<panel>
			<html>
				<div class="arcus">
					<i class="title fas fa-wrench" />
					<span style="font-size:30px; font-weight: 100;">Data &amp; Settings</span>
					<hr />
					<p>
						The data source which drives these dashboards is available to anyone with an Uber account. It takes about 1 day for Uber to compile your data. You'll download a .zip file containing
						<strong>trips_data.csv</strong>
						.
					</p>
					<p class="icon">
						<i class="fas fa-cloud-download-alt" />
						<a href="https://accounts.uber.com/privacy/downloadyourdata">Request Uber Data</a>
					</p>
					<hr />
					<br />
					<br />
					<br />
					<br />
					[Video Goes Here]
					<br />
					<br />
					<br />
					<br />
					<br />
					<hr />
					<h2>
						<b>Contact us:</b>
					</h2>
					<ul>
						<li>
							Main Site:
							<a href="https://arcusdata.io">Arcus Data</a>
						</li>
						<li>
							Arcus Blog:
							<a href="https://blog.arcusdata.io">Arcus Data Blog</a>
						</li>
						<li>
							GitHub:
							<a href="https://github.com/arcus-data">@arcus-data</a>
						</li>
						<li>
							Twitter:
							<a href="https://twitter.com/arcusdata">@arcusdata</a>
						</li>
					</ul>
				</div>
			</html>
		</panel>
	</row>
</dashboard>